[{"answer": "Well, of course, it's a little funny to watch a senator or a congressman who got himself elected by promising the citizen of his state that he would go to Washington to reform government, not raises taxes to pay for our problems.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "How are you going to avoid being chopped out the boat?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "I'm in favor of not raising taxes on all the American people, and as you know the American people quite rightly understand that politicians who say, I'm going to tax the rich, have not finished the sentence.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "Why do you care?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Well, there were three periods of growth or low growth during the Bush years.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Now what if we had carried -- what if we had carried along the Bush rate of growth of the eight years before Obama?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Very interesting this debate now in the Republican Party, especially involving Grover Norquist.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "I'm doing great, Piers, how are you?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Well, I think what you heard Grover say and what others have said is that we do need more revenues.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "Well, it's not really an ideological difference.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "What's the ideological difference if in the end wealthier people in America are all paying a little bit more tax?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "It's all about raising revenue through taxing the wealthier Americans a little bit more, isn't it?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Well, I think Chris Christie did job number one when Sandy came through as governor.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "I'm not fearing anybody.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Who would you most fear coming up against whoever the Democrat candidate will be in 2016?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think about that.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "You don't look in the mirror some mornings and think, I'm an icon?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "There's the old saying, of all the people who don't like me, just think of the millions who have never heard of me.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "Do you ever get anyone have a go at you?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Actually it was really an easy book to write.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "When you finished the book, what did you think of your life?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "Well, it's kind of -- you can't think about all of that at once.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "What do you -- what do you make of what's happened to you in those 80 years?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "I'm very happy right now.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Are you a happy guy?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "As happy as you've ever been?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "Yes, I did.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "Did you ever meet him?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "We had a drink together.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "Did you go drinking together?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "I didn't check the labels.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Jack Daniels?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "Did I say that?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "I probably did, I probably did.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "Did you make up this morning and have a quick you know?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "I think some people have more tolerance, you know, for smoking pot than others, and I know people who can take one hit and just go to sleep completely.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "Do you take a lot of it?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "I think it's progress, and I think it's, you know, a great step forward and people are finally growing up and looking around the room and checking things out.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "Now what do you make of that?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Maybe they'll have a coffee house.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "Are you planning a vacation there soon?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "Why not.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "You can have the Willie Nelson coffee chain, couldn't you?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "That would be really hard to say, because, you know, this is -- I just recorded a song with with Dolly Parton that I think is the best song that -- she wrote it.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "If you were consigned to a desert island and you could only listen to one song endlessly on a permanent replay, what would you choose?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "And I told her, I think this is the best song I've heard in a long time.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "I believe that.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "Do you really believe that?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "I do know it would work.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "That could be a strategy that works?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "Well, as you probably know I'm completely against war.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "When you look at the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan, what do you think about America's position in the world, its foreign policy in particular, in the last 12 years or so?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "Well, if you believe in the bible, where it says two things.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "Do you see any chance of actual peace in the Middle East?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "Yes, I'm glad he got re-elected.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "Were you pleased he got re- elected?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "I'm not really.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "I mean, how would you describe yourself?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "Well, I have voted, yes.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "You never voted for anybody?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "Did you -- did you this time?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "ELSON: Well, I had all kinds of excuses.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "I really felt like Obama was going to win, that he didn't really need one more vote that he already had sown up.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "You didn't feel passionately enough about either candidate?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I've partied all my life, and, you know, when I was a young I had a BB gun, I had a rubber gun, I had shotguns and rifles and all those things, and I went deer hunting and bear hunting.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "And what do you make of the gun debate in America?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "Yes, they are.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Talented guys your sons?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "Very proud of them.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "One of them is here, he did illustrations for the book?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "Very much.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Are you proud of them?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Well, yes, I think age has a lot to do with that, you know.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "Do you think you've become a better husband?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "Nothing.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "What have you learned about marriage?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Yes, the reason divorces are so expensive is they're worth it.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "You had a great line about divorce?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "And yet, although you say that, you also -- always stayed fond of your ex's, am I right?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "I do think it's important to -- you know, especially if you have children which we do, you know, you should stay friends and -- with your ex-wives.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "You must thought that was important?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "Well, you said properly in love.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "So if I was to ask you, how many of all the girls you've loved before we would reach how many would it be?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Well, I wouldn't -- what I said, I wouldn't have put it in there, but --", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "How would you define properly?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "How many times have you been in love in your life?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "Well, for the moment she is.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "Is she the -- is she the real love of your life, would you say?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "Do I ever sing songs to her?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "Hundred percent, yes.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "Are you a romantic at heart?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "The greatest moment of my life that doesn't involve children or women?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "That's a difficult one.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "If I could let you relive a moment, what would you choose?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "Every time I go do a show, where I show up and they show up, and they come and clap and pay good money to hear -- you know, hear me sing songs, it doesn't get any better than that.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "What's the a great life for you personally, for whatever reason?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "Willie, I could talk to you all day.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I don't think I was an evil man, I was just like a Texas businessman, that's all.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "Do you like being, for what you were, the most evil man on television?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "Especially with his own family.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "Isn't it?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "Of course I do, it is wonderful.", "docId": "121126pmt", "aSentId": 647, "question": "But did you like the reputation?", "qSentId": 646}]